Guide to the PricewaterhouseCoopers Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Price Waterhouse Series VI: Digital files
  - Subseries VI.2: Database
    - Inmagic database of correspondence from G. O. May files, as cataloged by PW information service. The documents descibed in this database are a part of G. O. May files series (correspondence by subject). Hard copy printout available at Paper - Centennial Research - Reference Materials subseries. (Box 97)
- Price Waterhouse Series VII: Books and Monographs
  - Reports of the Tax Court of the United States, Vols 32 - 38, Washington: United States Government Printing Office, Apr. 1, 1959 - Sep. 30, 1962, (7 volumes) (Box 97)
  - [Book on accounting], n.p., n.d., 6.5 x 2.75 x 2) (Box 98)
    [In German]
  - Allen, David Grayson; McDermott, Kathleen Accounting for Success: A History of Price Waterhouse in America, 1980-1990, Boston: Harvard Business School Press, 1993 (Box 98)
  - Anyon, James T Recollections of the Early Days of American Accountancy 1883-1893, n.p., 1925 (Box 97)
  - Arthur Andersen & Co. The First Sixty Years, Chicago, IL, 1974 (Box 97)
    [In 1906 Arthur Andersen joins the Chicago office of Price Waterhouse and Co., but soon leaves, dissatisfied by the slow pace of advancement. In 1913 he starts his own company, which ultimately became a large competitor firm. ]
  - Brown, Richard, ed A. History of Accounting and Accountants, Edinburgh: T. C. & E. C. Jack, 1905 (Box 97)
  - Bryant, J. C. New Book-Keeping, Elementary and Practical, Eighth Edition, Buffalo, NY: Published by the Author, 1882 (Box 42)
    [Needs Repair]
  - DeMond, C. W. Price, Waterhouse & Co. in America: A History of Public Accounting Firm, New York: Arno Press, 1980 (Box 97)
  - Forstmann Woolen Company Skilled Hands, [Passaic, NJ]: 1944 (Box 97)
  - Foster, Wood B. A Practical System of Book-Keeping by Double and Single Entry, Fourth Edition, Boston: James French, 1844 (Box 97)
  - Geijsbeek, John B. Ancient Double-Entry Bookkeeping, Houston: Scholars Books Co Reprint, c1914; reprint, 1974 (Box 98)
  - Jones, Edgar True and Fair: A History of Prince Waterhouse, London: Hamish Hamilton, 1995 (Box 97)
  - Meservey, A. B. Bookkeeping, Single and Double Entry, Boston: Thompson, Brown, & Co, 1883 (Box 97)
  - Metz, Herman A. ed. Manual of Accounting and Business Procedure of the City of New York, New York: Department of Finance, 1909 (Box 97)
  - Stevens, Mark The Big Eight, New York, Collier Books, Macmillan Publishing Co., 1981 (Box 98)
  - Stevens, Mark The Accounting Wars, New York, Collier Books, Macmillan Publishing Co., 1986 (Box 98)
  - Swanson, Theodor Touche Ross: A Biography, Touche Ross & Co, 1972 (Box 98)